《吸血鬼后裔》前情提要
Previously on Legacies...
你不想让我说你所有朋友
You don't want me to point out all your friends
都忘记了你的存在
have forgotten you ever existed.
自我被乔西攻击后醒过来
When I woke up from that spell Josie blasted me with,
你就突然出现在了我混乱的脑子里
you popped into my messed-up brain
像致幻剂副作用  片段闪回一样
like an acid flashback.
我本来要告诉大家我回来了的
gonna tell everyone that I was back.
但我看见了兰登和乔西在一起幸福的样子
But then I saw Landon and Josie and how happy they were.
怪物回来了
The monsters are back.
我不知道这会如何停止  原因是什么
I have no idea how or why
或是否会停止
or if it's gonna stop.
- 丽兹  她认识了一个新的吸血鬼  - 塞巴斯蒂安
- Lizzie-- she-she met this new vampire.   - Sebastian?
你在跟谁说话呢  哥们
Who you talking to, man?
对了  他看不见我
Oh, yes. No, he can't see me.
他想要我们唤醒他
He wants for us to wake him up.
- 你想知道什么  - 你是哪类吸血鬼
- What do you wish to know?  - What kind of vamp you are.
我喝了很多人的血
I fed on so many humans.
鹅卵石上沾满了鲜血
The cobblestones-- they ran red with blood.
既然如此
Well, in that case...
- 所以你叫韦德  - 你是谁
- So you're name's Wade, then.  - Who are you?
你的朋友
A friend.
新奥尔良
卢梭饭店
我试图欺骗自己
* I tried to fool myself *
在深夜等着你
* Waiting for you late at night... *
你多大了
And how old are you claiming to be?
21岁  差不多吧
21... ish.
但我知道
* But I know... *
放轻松  我们这儿被称作  大放纵  是有原因的
Relax. It's called "the Big Easy" for a reason.
我为什么相信
* Why do I believe... *
我是弗雷娅
I'm Freya.
我听说你一直在找我
I hear you've been asking around the Quarter for me.
我是乔西
I'm Josie.
我是塞瓦托尔学校的学生
I'm a student at the Salvatore School.
- 你知道神秘瀑布镇吧  - 我听说过
- Mystic Falls?  - Yeah, I've heard of it.
我妻子在考虑让我们的儿子去那上学
My wife's got an eye on it for our son.
我需要你的帮助
I kind of need your help.
我在找一个逆转的咒语
There's this spell that I'm kind of trying to reverse engineer.
我相信你的老师会帮你的
I'm sure one of your teachers can help you with that.
是一个古老的日本黑魔法净化咒语
An ancient Japanese black magic purge spell?
欺骗  欺骗  欺骗
* Lying, lying, lying... *
你一个学生不能随意
Those aren't the kind of spells
接触使用这种咒语
school kids should be messing with.
你该回家了
You should go home.
等等
Wait.
你家里有一些
You have photos in your home
你认不出来的人的照片
of someone you don't recognize.
感觉你明明认识他们  但是却不认识
Feels like you should know them, but you don't?
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
我们都忘记了些什么人
We've all forgotten people.
这些都不重要
It doesn't matter what I say.
我说的那个咒语
The spell that I need is the only way
是能让你记起来的唯一方式
that you're gonna remember for yourself.
现在到了这次参观的
All right, now, on to our tour's
最后也是最重要的一站
final and most important stop--
前门
the front door.
从这里出去回酒店吧  爱你
Use it to get back to your hotel. Love you.
别玩我了  我是为英联邦纪念日来的
Quit playing. I came up for Commonwealth Day.
给我看些有趣的东西
Now show me the cool stuff.
这里是学校  没什么有趣的东西
This is school. There's nothing cool to see.
是个满是吸血鬼  女巫  和狼人的学校
It's a school for vampires, witches and werewolves,
所以我不看见点魔法世界
so there's no way I'm leaving
的东西  是不会走的
without seeing something Harry Potter.
凯姆
Kym?
我说最后一遍  这没什么能参观的东西
For the last time, there is nothing... to... see.
焚化
Incendia!
丽兹  我们只有困住它才能阻止
Lizzie, we have to trap it so Malivore
马里之洼继续放出另外的怪物
can't send another monster.
焚化它可不符合我们的目的
Incinerating it kind of defeats the purpose?
好吧好吧
Okay, fine.
咒语
Glacies corporis.
你刚才说什么来着
You were saying?
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第6集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
神秘瀑布镇  英联邦纪念日
警长
Sheriff.
- 嘿  - 所以你能看见我啊
- Hey. - Oh. So you can see me?
你上周不联系我  搞得我以为我是隐形的呢
I thought maybe I was invisible after you ghosted me last week.
真的很抱歉
Yeah, I'm-I'm really sorry about that.
我女儿那有点事情
You know, something came up with my daughters.
我在学着放手
And I'm learning to let them go
让她们自己解决问题
and figure things out on their own.
翻 译  Krystal
但显然很不成功
Just really suck at that.
我知道什么感觉
I know the feeling.
- 那个  - 所有单位  神秘阀门处
- Uh, you know...  - All units, potential
可能发生了起谋杀案  收到请回复
187 at Mystic Tap. Please respond.
翻 译  RossyGeng
收到
I'm on it.
不管你要说什么  记得下次如果我给你机会
Whatever you were about to say, make sure the next time
让你说时  你能好好说完
I give you a chance to say it, you actually follow through.
翻 译  艾艾  晁安
翻 译  Carousel
我已经割到自己不下5次了
I have done that, like, five times.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
被纸割伤能死人吗
Is it possible to die from a paper cut?
小心点  现在这可是镇上最重要的胳膊
Careful. That's the best arm in town now.
我看看
Let me see.
是的
Yeah.
很致命
It's fatal.
特效：小螺号
你们俩  别调情了
Hey, you two, quit slacking.
明天的庆典可不能被
Tomorrow's festivities will not be thrown off
校 对   晁安
荷尔蒙过盛的青少年影响
by hormonal teenagers.
当然  议员
Sure thing, Councilman.
特 效   麦 斯
是被一个白人老政治家毁了吧
Ruined by an old, white guy politician, though?
完全有这个可能性
Totally plausible.
那种人怎么赢得选举的
How did that guy win an election?
民主
Democracy...
不再是以前的样子了
isn't what it used to be.
我得去训练了
Hey, I got to head to practice.
但你受伤了
But you're hurt.
我还是能帮到我的团队的
I can still help the team win.
懂了  之后见
Gotcha. See you after?
除非你跟我一起去理疗
Not unless you're coming to physical therapy with me.
我这些日子过得可精彩了
My life's a real party these days.
如果你想见我
You ever want to see me,
可以约我出去
you should probably just ask me out.
别那副表情  赶紧过来
Don't "gah" me. Get your ass under here.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
找你  你本应该负责看着
Looking for you. You were supposed
马里之洼的传送门的
to be keeping an eye on the portal to Malivore.
我就是在看着
I'm literally on top of it.
显然看得不够仔细
Not on top of it enough.
今早一个僵尸溜进了校园
A zombie snuck onto campus this morning.
你确定是从传送门出来的吗
I mean, are you sure it's from the portal?
我整个晚上都在这
I've been here all night.
它的头骨上刻着马里之洼的标志
It has the mark of Malivore carved into its skull.
显然是从传送门出来的
It's obviously from the portal.
也许你太专注于和麻瓜调情了
Maybe you were too busy flirting with the muggle.
我不是在调情  是在试图融入
I wasn't flirting. I was blending in.
不管你用什么办法  别调情了
Hey, by all means, flirt away.
你越快放弃兰登
The faster you get over Landon,
我就能尽早不再担心乔西的幸福
the sooner I can stop worrying about Josie's happiness.
我们把那个僵尸锁起来了  所以说不用再
We locked the zombie up, which means no more portal duty
看着传送门了  今天咱们俩可以一起玩了
is required, and you and I can hang out today.
说了这么多
Why is that last part harder
为什么我就觉得你最后一句最难理解呢
for me to understand than all the rest?
我要是去找乔西
If I spend any time with Josie,
我会忍不住爆出你的秘密的
I will inevitably blow your secret.
你要是不想让她伤心
You want to protect her from heartbreak,
就跟我一起吧
you're stuck with me.
好吧
Okay.
回神了  拉斐尔
Um, Earth to Rafael.
凤凰可没有超级力量
Phoenixes don't have super strength.
我的错  我分心了
My-my bad. I'm-I'm distracted.
丽兹和霍普现在是朋友了吗
Are Lizzie and Hope friends now?
这是个麻烦
It is a problem.
如果丽兹
Look, I'll be lucky
不说我的坏话的话我就是走运了  哥们
if Lizzie doesn't talk trash about me, dude.
说你也是你应得的
Deserved trash. Earned trash.
香汗淋漓  健身房性爱什么的
Sweaty, gym-sex trash.
抱歉
Sorry.
你知道你需要什么吗
You know what you need?
- 一个僚机  - 我的天拜托
A wingman.   Oh, by-by which
- 你可别是在说  - 我
- I pray you do not mean... -  Me.
我帮你打掩护
I can help run interference.
你去吧  来点行动  去吧
You get in there, make a move. Come on.
乔西和我很愿意和别的情侣一起玩
Josie and I can use a couple for double dates.
你成功的时候就知道谢我了
You can thank me when it works.
你一定会的
You will.
抬你的桌子吧  哥们
Lift the table, man.
不好意思  你说
* Excuse me, you say... *
咒语
Harae-tamai Kioku
Yomigaerashi-tamae.
念咒语时  信念很重要
In the spell, conviction matters.
你需要专注于你的目的  头脑清醒
You need to be clear of mind and purpose.
否则  不仅不会
If not, instead of
净化大脑中的超自然影响
purging the supernatural influence in the mind,
反而会使它更坚固  永久地留存住它
you'll end up solidifying it, making it permanent.
真有听起来的这么严重吗
Is that as bad as it sounds?
一不小心就会抹去你想要
You'd erase the very memories
带回的那些记忆的
you're trying to bring back.
你是怎么
How did you
找到这条咒语的
even find this spell?
我为了救我妹妹  从一把古剑中汲取出来的
I siphoned it from an ancient sword to save my sister's life?
奇怪的短篇故事  我在日记里读到过
Weird story short, I read in this diary
它是如何让她恢复所有记忆的
how it returned all of her memories somehow.
魔法和隐私并不相容
Magic and privacy don't mix well.
是我妻子  她今晚
That's my wife. She's on
照顾我们的儿子尼克
Nik duty tonight-- our kid.
不好意思
Excuse me.
是  我还在酒吧
Yup. Yeah, I'm still at the bar.
尼克怎么样了
How's Nik doing?
除却平凡的日常
* Out of the ordinary every day *
你做了什么
* What did you do *
你知道吗
* Did you know *
你跟随的是谁
* And who do you follow? *
她是谁
Who is she?
我知道你有事瞒着我
I knew you were hiding something from me.
告诉我
So tell me,
我们为何会忘记同一个人呢
how is it we both forgot the same person?
如果你不先告诉我的话
And if you didn't tell me that to begin with,
我只能认为是你还没决定好
I can only assume it's because you haven't decided
用这个咒语去做什么
what you're going to do with that spell.
是吗
Have you?
这个女孩是谁
Who is that girl?
咒语
Harae-tamai Kioku Yomigaerashi-tamae!
我的眼睛
Oh, my eyes!
这是什么巫术
What is this sorcery?!
这东西叫马鞭草
It's called "vervain," I think.
很酷是吧
It's cool, right?
你做得很好
You did great!
我就说这一定管用的
Told you this would work.
放开我  你们两个蠢货
Unhand me, you turnips.
我吸了个猎物
I had one drink.
没错  你吸的那个叫韦德
Yeah, that drink's name was Wade.
- 我觉得是  - 我并没有
- I think. - I did not even
杀了你的宝贝韦恩
kill your precious Wayne.
快放开我趁我还
Now unhand me before I...
该死  你拧了他干嘛
Damn. Why'd you do that?
可能是因为今天我受够了别人说无礼的话
Maybe because I'm tired of people giving me lip today.
我不管今天联邦日你有多古怪
I don't care how geeked out you are over Commonwealth Day.
我要送你坐下一班出城的车
I'm putting you on the next bus out of town.
- 但我这身衣裳是手工做的  - 我不想看
- But I had this costume handmade. - Yeah, don't even
你穿得这身奇装异服
get me started on all the things wrong with you wearing that.
我个人非常支持女性
I personally support a woman's right
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
随心所欲的穿着
to wear whatever she wants.
别催我做事  凯勒布
Stop trying to marsh my mellow, Kaleb.
我准备好了自己会走的
I'll leave when I'm good and ready.
- 我告诉妈去  - 我还告诉爹去呢
- Oh. I'll call Mom. - I'll call Dad.
我  该死
I... Damn it.
你没别的事干了吗
Don't you got something else to do
非得在这掺和
other than sit here and chime in
与你无关的事
on matters that don't concern you?
没错  没错
Yeah. Yeah.
我要带上赛巴斯提安  带他回学校
I'm gonna grab Sebastian, and I'm gonna take him to
萨尔茨曼博士的办公室
Dr. Saltzman's office at the high school until
直到联邦日结束
Commonwealth Day's over.
办公室里没人  所以他醒来之前都不会有人的
It's empty so no one should be there when he wakes up.
你说的没人  指的是丽兹是吗
By "no one," you mean Lizzie, right?
你还没告诉她
You haven't told her.
我是打算要
I was... I was gonna...
兄弟啊  拜托
Dude, come on.
她肯定会很生我气的
She's gonna be so pissed at me.
是今早的那个金发女吗
Is that the blonde from this morning?
我不小心
I sort of accidentally
让她以为自己得了精神分裂
made her think she was having a psychotic break.
这事没救了
That's not gonna go well.
我知道
I know.
这是我们一定要保密  爱丽丝
We have to keep this a secret, Alice.
尤其是我处在改选期间
Especially now with my reelection campaign.
再联系
I'll call you back.
庆典明天才开始
Festivities aren't until tomorrow.
你行头不错  后退
Nice costume, buddy, but back off.
我说我想出来溜达
When I said that I wanted to hang out,
可没想到遇上这事
this is not what I had in mind.
谁发现他的
Who even found him?
谁发现他烂成这样的
Or what's left of him?
阿丽莎·常晨跑的时候
Alyssa Chang on her morning jog.
也算是好事  否则这里就会
Good thing, too. Otherwise, this place would be
挤满警察
crawling with police.
你觉得我们遇上什么怪物了
What kind of monster do you think we're dealing with?
克柔投安
A Croatoan.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
一种预感吧
Call it a hunch.
克柔投安
好了  小队
Okay, squad.
我们遇到了个问题
We have a problem,
我们缺了个巫师  因为乔西去了里士满
and we're down a witch because Josie's in Richmond
为了联邦纪念日
for Commonwealth Day.
这对我们很不利  因为
Which is bad for us, because...
克柔投安进了校门
A Croatoan came through the portal.
杀了个议员
And it killed a councilman.
克柔投安是什么
What the hell's a Croatoan?
等等
Hold up.
是罗诺克的消亡殖民地
The lost colony of Roanoke.
- 真的吗  你们都不知道吗  - 我知道
- Seriously? Not one of you?   - I'll play.
罗诺克嘛  是北美第一批英国殖民地之一
Roanoke. It's one of the first English settlements
直到后来毫无踪迹的消失了
in North America until it just vanished without a trace.
唯一存留的一样东西就是
And the only thing left behind
刻在树上的
was a word carved on a tree:
克柔投安
"Croatoan."
怎么了  我是个历史控
What? I'm a history nerd.
不然我为啥来参加联邦日
Why else would I be here for Commonwealth Day?
不用理她  她的探视特权
I-Ignore her. Her visitation privileges
- 要被取消了  - 怪物
- are about to be revoked.   - The monster
来学校了  正在找兰登
is here, and it's after Landon,
所以我们要把他转移到安全的地方
so we need to get him somewhere safe.
好的
Okay, um,
无意冒犯  但为什么瀑布镇的女孩
no offense, but why is some girl
来这给我们发号施令
from Mystic Falls giving us orders?
- 因为她是个狼人  - 因为她是个巫师
- Oh, it's because she's a wolf.  - Because she's a witch.
最重要的  她懂得如何打怪
Most importantly, she knows how to kill monsters.
- 这太好了  - 等等同志们
- That's so cool.   - Wait, guys.
僵尸怎么办呢  我以为马里之洼
What about the zombie? I thought Malivore
- 一次只能释放一个怪物  - 没错
- could only release one monster at a time. - Yeah.
我们都以为这样
That's what we all thought.
你怎么知道
How the hell
马里之洼的
do you know about Malivore?
我告诉她的
Oh, I-I filled her in.
没错  她
Yeah. She...   Mm-hmm.
她干掉了鬼怪
She took down the Oni,
杀了牛头怪
and she killed the Minotaur.
虽然其实算是我杀的
Although that was actually really more me.
等等  还有牛头怪呢
Wait, wait. There was a Minotaur?
没错  不是哪件事都有你
Yeah. Not everything's about you.
好了  这样的话
All right. So, then,
有什么计划  狼女巫
what's the plan, Miss Were-witch?
计划就是我会带走兰登
The plan is that I will take Landon,
给他施屏障咒保护
put a barrier spell around him...   Oh.
她的意思是
Wh-What she means
其他人都参加联邦日的时候
is that I will babysit Landon while everyone else is
我来照顾兰登  与此同时霍普来完成她的
at Commonwealth Day while Hope does her whole
除魔大业
monster hunting deal.
这个主意不错
That is a great idea.
她应该和谁一起呢  拉斐尔
And you know who should go with her? Rafael.
我可以帮忙搜查
I can help with research.
- 保你住的酒店安全  - 好了
- Yeah, from the safety of your hotel room. - Okay.
- 超级小队可以解散了  - 超级小队
- Super squad disassemble or whatever. - Super squad.
酷哦  行了走吧
Cool. Okay, great.
完事了  还没吆喝呢
No? Not done here?
计划很棒  能让你
It's a good plan. It keeps you
尽可能地远离兰登
as far away from Landon as possible.
比起和他共处
I'm less worried about me being with Landon
我更担心你把我的秘密告诉他
than I am about you blowing my secret to him.
放心  我就问问他星球大战
Relax.  I'll just ask him about StarWar
之类的
or something,
他就会滔滔不绝的讲
and then he'll talk the whole time.
你没什么
You have nothing
好担心的
to worry about.
好吧
Okay.
妈
Mom.
抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you
太晚了
so... late.
或者说  太早了
Or early.
随便吧
Whatever it is.
我遇到了问题
I'm in a situation.
我找到了找回大家马里之洼记忆的办法
I found a way to bring back everyone's Malivore memories.
我觉得这样真的会
I just think it could really...
让大家
hurt, um...
很痛苦
people.
我不知道该怎么办了
I just don't know what to do.
我得承认
I got to admit, it's...
离镇一会儿还挺好
it's nice to get a break from town.
人群还是我令我心率加快
You know, crowds still get my heart racing.
和大家共处
It can't be easy
还是很难适应
to adjust to being around people.
和你聊天很有帮助
Talking with you helps.
我  你甚至都不认识我
Me? You don't even know me.
但我觉得我认识你
But I feel like I do.
就好像  我应该认识你还是怎么的
It's like I'm-I'm supposed to or something.
听着
Look, look,
我知道你肯定已经有几个
I know you must already have a couple...
有好多小伙子或者姑娘对你有兴趣
dozen guys or-or girls that are interested in you.
我
I-I...
严格来说  我没在谈恋爱
Technically, um, I'm not seeing anyone.
那你应该知道
Then you should know that...
我可不怕技术性问题
I'm not afraid of technicalities.
那是什么
What is that?
学校档案里的
A dark object
一样黑暗的东西
from the school archives.
一旦我点燃了它
Once I light it,
超自然的东西就都进不来了
nothing supernatural can get inside.
这应该能防止你们被干掉
This should prevent you from becoming Croa-toast.
我看到你和霍普一起玩儿了
Um, I saw you and Hope hanging out.
你知不知道她有没有男朋友呢
Do you know if she's seeing anyone?
你不是应该专注于乔西吗
Shouldn't you be focusing on Josie?
是啊  我是帮拉斐尔问的
Uh, yeah. I was asking for Rafael.
很好  因为既然你已经给
Good. Because now you've watered
乔西的永生花花园浇了水
the garden of Josie's eternal flower,
我觉得你就应该将其视为神圣的
I would think that you would hold that to be sacred.
请告诉我这是个比方
Please tell me that's a metaphor.
我的意思是  一旦结合
My point is, once you've boned,
就永远不能分开了
you can never unbone.
- 不是比喻  - 而且你要是看上了别人
Not a metaphor.   And it would be a real crap guy move
你就真的是个大猪蹄子
for you to shift your sights elsewhere.
上帝为证  我永远也不会这样的
For the record, I would never do that.
而且
Also...
我们没有
we didn't.
不好意思  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
虽然这不关你的事吧  但是没有什么
Not that it's any of your business, but there was no...
浇水  结合  随便什么
Watering? Boning? Whatever.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这样一切都变了
This changes everything.
怎么说
How?
没什么
Never mind.
告诉我  你觉得伊沃克人
Tell me, where do you stand...
怎么样
on Ewoks?
我是说  他们跟泰迪熊差不多
I mean, they're basically teddy bears,
谁会讨厌泰迪熊呢
and who hates teddy bears?
如果你讨厌泰迪熊  那就是你的问题  这个意思
If you hate teddy bears, that's on you. That's all I'm saying.
而且还是干掉了邪恶帝国的泰迪熊
Especially teddy bears who took down the Empire.
我是这么觉得的
That's where I stand on Ewoks.
这太棒了
That's fascinating.
我要去睡一会儿
I'm gonna go take a nap.
我还以为那个蜡烛
I thought the candle
能把恶魔挡在外头呢
was supposed to keep the monsters out.
我也是  它应该是能保你不受恶魔侵害的
Me, too. It was supposed to keep them from getting to you.
丽兹  它没有找上我
Lizzie, it didn't go after me.
是找上你了
It's after you.
所以有超快速还能永生
So superspeed and immortality?
当吸血鬼可真挺好的
Being a vampire is pretty sweet.
做吸血鬼也有坏处
There's downsides to being a vamp, too.
会伤害到别人
You can hurt people.
我觉得你不会
Well, I don't think you would.
不管是不是超快速
Well, superspeed or not,
萨尔茨曼博士的书里我什么也没找到
I'm not finding anything in Dr. Saltzman's books.
因为你找错书了
'Cause you've got the wrong book.
跟你说过了  历史是我喜欢的
I told you, history's my jam.
根据这些荒诞的故事
And according to these old wives' tales,
这个怪物就像是
this monster's, like,
一个捕蝇草  或者什么和章鱼的混合体
a Venus flytrap or something mixed with an octopus.
他们把食物塞在喉咙里  这样受害者
They stab their food in the throat so their victims
就叫不出声  然后他们用酸性的唾液
can't scream, and then they dissolve them
把受害者融化到什么都不剩
with acid-like saliva until there's nothing left.
食物  是说人吧
And by food, you mean people.
说谎的人
More like liars.
是这么说的  它们的猎物是有秘密的人
Legend has it they hunt fools keeping secrets.
所以我们对彼此
So let's be completely honest
坦白吧
with each other.
所以  你的书里还说了什么
So-so, what else does your book say?
消逝者可以由有魔力的女巫召唤
Croatoans can be summoned by powerful witches.
所以罗诺克曾有过女巫
So there was a witch in Roanoke.
她叫做卡桑德拉
SEBASTIAN: Her name was Cassandra.
我可以告诉你更多
I could tell you more about her,
我亲爱的大头菜
my dear turnip,
如果你放弃这种对爱情的
if you abort this feeble attempt
无力追逐  然后放我走
at romance and let me go.
再说一次
MG: For the last time,
我不是棵植物
I'm not a vegetable.
而且我们  只是朋友
And we're... just friends.
而且  我们为什么要
Besides, why should we believe
相信你说的话
anything you say?
因为我在场
Because I was there.
我需要帮助
I need help.
为什么所有人都觉得
Why does everyone assume
我力大无比
I have superstrength?
相信我  没人这么觉得
Trust me, no one thinks that.
好吧  我来接
Fine, I'll get it.
喂
Hello?
是我  MG
MG: It's me, MG.
- 我有些情报  - 说快点
I got some intel.   Talk fast.
显然  过去
Apparently, back in the day,
这个旧世界的吸血鬼
this sketchy vamp of the Old World
会啃食罗诺克的定居者
was nibbling on the settlers of Roanoke.
有一个他
There was this witch that he...
讨好的女巫
was... courting.
她想要查出村里那个
She wanted to get to the bottom of who the secret killer
神秘的杀手是谁
was in the village.
她说她要创造出
She said she was gonna manifest
这个能够闻出其中
this demon creature that could
谁是凶手的怪物
sniff out the killer in their midst.
一个靠秘密为生的怪物
A monster that fed on secrets.
秘密啊
Secrets, you say.
这可太棒了
Well, that's great,
因为这里没人有秘密
because there's no one keeping any of those around here.
我们要怎么杀掉它
How do we kill it?
还在查
That's a work in progress.
查快点
Work faster.
这个该死的玩意儿突破了我的防线
The damn thing waltzed through my barrier like it was...
就像入无人之境
immune.
因为只有召唤了它的女巫
Because only the witch
才能毁掉它
who summoned it can destroy it.
这就是问题了  因为她已经死了快五百年了
That's a problem, 'cause she's been dead for, like, 500 years.
我们要死了  想点办法
We're about to die. Figure something out.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
接到你的电话了
Got your call.
大概这不是约会了吧
I take it it's not a date.
我们还在试图
MAC: We're still trying
查出到底发生了什么
to piece together what happened.
觉得你可能有些帮助
Thought you might be able to shed some light.
动物袭击
An animal attack.
Animal attack.
这里经常会有
Mm-hmm. Yeah, we get them here all the time.
你可以看看警方的报告
You can check the police reports.
我有个朋友在联调局
Well, I have a friend at the FBI
我要送去见证
that I'm sending the forensics to
他可能有不同的说法
who may say otherwise.
最好你这次
I-It would be better
能相信我
if you could just trust me on this one.
这要求可挺有趣的
Oh. Well, that's an interesting request,
尤其是对于在袭击时间前后
especially from someone that a witness placed here
有目击者证明其在场的人
around the time of the attack.
这个怪物在找秘密
LIZZIE: This monster is hunting secrets,
不是你  所以至少它
not you, so at least it has
- 还算有些品味  不像我姐姐  - 但问题就在这里
some taste, unlike my sister.   But that's the thing,
不管马里之洼和这些怪物说了什么
no matter what Malivore tells the monsters,
他们总是会跟从主要的指令
they always follow their prime directive first.
所以不管什么秘密  告诉我
So tell me whatever secret you're keeping,
或许它就会停下了
and maybe it'll stop.
是有关霍普的吗
Is it about Hope?
是有关霍普的对吧
It's about Hope, isn't it?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
反正这也没用
Thing was useless anyway.
至少我有个想法了
Well, at least I had an idea.
我也有了
I just had one, too.
你能让我们隐身然后打开他的牢笼吗
Can you make us invisible and break open his cell?
大概可以吧  为什么
I guess. Why?
我们要做所有伟大的科幻片作者都会做的
We're gonna do what every great sci-fi franchise does--
金刚对哥斯拉  异型大战铁血战士
Kong versus Godzilla, Alien versus Predator...
我们要互舔吗
We're gonna suck?
这是亵渎神明的  不  我们要
That's blasphemy. No, we're gonna...
我们要让怪物对怪物
we're gonna let the monsters fight.
这是臆想
Oh, this is a nerdgasm,
不算个计划
not a plan.
行啊  那就说出真相
Fine. Then just tell the truth.
咒语
Invisique.
我说过了吧  呆子
LIZZIE : I told you, nerd.
- 嘘  - 你才嘘
- LANDON: Shh!  - LIZZIE: You shh!
我有个更好的计划
I have a better plan.
丑人  在这儿
Hey, ugly. Over here.
做得好  但是那坚持不了多久的  所以你就
Nice work, but that's not gonna hold it long, so just...
- 把秘密告诉我吧  - 做不到
- tell me the secret. -  I can't.
- 为什么  - 这会让乔西心碎的
- Why? - It would break Josie's heart.
- 所以这是关于乔西的  - 不  是关于我们所有人的
- So this is about Josie?  - No, it's about all of us.
丽兹  你什么时候
Lizzie, since when
对任何事情都守口如瓶了
have you kept your mouth shut about anything?
快告诉我
Just tell me.
好吧  这
Fine! It's...
咒语
HOPE: Silencio.
所以这是关于你的
so this is about you.
- 我们得离开这里  - 你到底在对
We have to get out of here. What are you
- 大家隐藏些什么  - 没时间了
- hiding from everyone? - HOPE: There's no time.
这些栅栏撑不住了
These bars aren't gonna hold.
我们得想办法阻止它
We have to find some way to stop it.
MG正在努力
MG is working on it.
还有  因为兰登  现在有一个
Also, because of Landon, there is now
僵尸在逃
a zombie on the loose.
- 这是个好主意  - 好吧
It was a good idea. Okay,
一次一只怪物
one monster at a time.
拉夫  带兰登去找萨尔茨曼博士
Raf, take Landon to Dr. Saltzman.
丽兹和我会想办法吸引克柔投安的注意
Lizzie and I will find a way to keep the Croatoan busy.
出发吧
Let's go.
拜托  伙计  你听到她说的了
Hey, come on, man. You heard her.
我不明白为什么
SEBASTIAN: I don't understand why
我记不起更多了
I can't remember more.
卡珊德拉  她是我的挚爱
Cassandra, she was... my great love.
不过  宅女召唤了一个恶魔
KYM: Homegirl summoned a demon
来掐死你
to snuff you out, though.
她知道是我吗
Had she known it was me,
我相信她有她不同的做事方式
I believe she would have done things differently.
也许你该对那位女士
MG: Maybe you should have just been
诚实点  而不是
honest with the lady
像德古拉那样鬼鬼祟祟的
instead of skulking around here like Dracula.
弥尔顿  你给我们上了一堂课
A lesson in being honest
告诉我们要对自己喜欢的女人保持诚实
about the woman one fancies is particularly ironic
是非常讽刺的
coming from you, Milton.
你刚和瓦尔德莫斯教授
So you were just having a drink
喝了一杯  他就是那个被你打脸的人吗
with Professor Vardemus, the guy you punched in the face?
我认为我们言和最符合
I thought it was in everyone's best interest
大家的利益
that we make peace.
我回家后  然后  我只知道这些
I went home after, and... that's all I know.
你看起来是个好人  我想相信你
You seem like a nice guy. I want to believe you.
但你的名字出现在很多在处理这个
But your name pops up in a whole lot of police reports
镇上尸体的警察报告中
dealing with dead bodies in this town.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
听着  我理解你的怀疑
Listen, I understand your suspicions,
但我和酒吧里的那些人一点关系都没有
but I had absolutely nothing to do with those people in the bar.
你们的关系吗
And your relationships?
似乎你交往过的每个女人都有
Seems like every woman you're involved with
悲惨的结局
meets a tragic end.
这也是我不容易敞开心扉的原因之一
One of the reasons I don't open up so easily.
你丈夫也一样  对吧
And the same thing goes for your husband, right?
我知道他死的
I understand that he passed away under....
很蹊跷
questionable circumstances.
你也找过我
Oh, you looked me up, too.
几乎是在讨好我了
It's almost flattering.
公平合理
Only fair.
听着
Look...
我需要些东西
I need something.
最好是不在场证明  或者
Preferably an alibi, or...
我们应该等你律师来了再谈
we should probably stop talking until you lawyer up.
很抱歉你这么想
Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
但我已经有了
But I already have one,
而且无懈可击
and it's airtight.
那你为什么现在才告诉我
Then why are you only telling me about it now?
因为我希望你能相信我
'Cause I was hoping you'd trust me.
去吧
Go ahead.
多诺万
给他打个电话
Give him a call.
你要把一切都告诉兰登
You were gonna tell Landon everything.
- 我们说好了的  - 事情有变
We had a deal. Well, things changed.
乔西和兰登没有做爱
Josie and Landon didn't have sex, which means
这意味着你可能还会想着把
you might still want to plant your flag
- 他抢回来  - 等等  什么
on Muppet Treasure Island.   Wait. What?
安静地感受惊讶吧
Shh. Be surprised quietly.
还有个怪物在追我们呢  记得吗
There's still a monster chasing us, remember?
重新考虑了一下  你想怎么大声就怎么大声吧
On second thought, be as loud as you want.
因为我们彻底完蛋了
Because we are so screwed.
它以秘密为食  对吧
Uh, it feeds on secrets, right?
所以把所有的都告诉我
So let me have it, all of it.
我宁愿死得有尊严些
I prefer to die with dignity.
好吧  我先开始
Okay, fine, I'll start. Um...
我五年级的时候偷了你的玉蝴蝶夹
I stole your jade butterfly clip in fifth grade.
我最喜欢那个蝴蝶夹了
I loved that clip!
我们14岁的时候
HOPE: Well, I had a crush
我迷恋了乔西一个星期
on Josie for a week when we were 14.
读我的唇语  你们两个
Read my lips: the two of you
永远不会在一起
are never happening.
丽兹  集中注意力
Uh, Lizzie? Focus.
好吧
LIZZIE: Okay, um,
我不小心杀了你的仓鼠
I accidentally killed your hamster.
我趁你在期末考试时作弊
I siphoned you to cheat on finals.
什么
What?
我一直觉得你挺酷的
And I actually think you're kind of cool.
好吧  这不管用
HOPE: Okay, it's not working.
直到所有人都知道我们
It's not gonna stop until everyone knows
瞒着他们的秘密  我回来了
the secret we've been keeping from them: that I'm back.
我也是
I'm back, too.
咒语
Harae-tamai Kioku
Yomigaerashi-tamae!
阿拉里克
Alaric?
里克
Ric!
小
Jo!
真相在这
HOPE : Here's the truth.
兰登  我爱你
Landon, I love you.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Are you okay?
你这瘦身板就像一袋锤子一样掉了下去
Your skinny ass dropped like a bag of hammers.
我觉得我
I felt like I was...
被咒语击中
hit by a spell.
像是
Like,
万咒之母
the mother of all spells.
然后
And then there was...
霍普
...Hope.
我现在也想起来了
SEBASTIAN: I remember now, too.
原来只有些片段的地方
Where there were but fragments,
我现在看到了整个故事
I now see the whole story.
关于卡珊德拉
About Cassandra,
怪物
the monster.
我们如何杀死它的
How we killed it.
她给了我这个  这个纪念物
She gave me this, this token.
她说这会保护我
She said that it would protect me.
从  怪物那吗
From... the monster?
不  来自殖民地时期的领导阶层
No. From the colony leadership.
他们让卡珊德拉去找那个
They asked Cassandra to find the monster that was...
把他们吓坏了的怪物
that was terrorizing them.
但她确实爱着我
But she did love me.
所以她甚至召唤了一些更邪恶的东西
So she summoned something even... worse.
这样就能找出
Something that
那些清教徒伪君子对村子
would ferret out the lies those Puritan hypocrites
里其他人隐瞒的谎言
were concealing from the rest of the village.
以免与他们找到我
Keep them from finding me.
然后克柔投安去找他了
Then the Croatoan went ham.
将所有人的记忆抹去
Wiped everyone out.
是的  正如你所知道的  弥尔顿
SEBASTIAN: Yeah. As you well know, Milton,
无人不在说谎
everybody lies.
当我发现卡珊德拉在策划什么
When I found out what Cassandra was plotting,
我试图阻止他
I tried to stop her.
她替我保守秘密
She was keeping my secret.
我担心她会成为目标
I feared that she'd become a target.
所以她把我变成这样
So she desiccated me...
以保护我的安全
to keep me safe.
在那个州  我看着那个克柔投安
In the state, I watched the Croatoan
在她驱散它之前就把她的四肢撕了下来
tear her limb from limb before she could dispel it.
她死后我无法帮助她
Unable to help her as she died.
天啊
Damn.
这是她的
This was hers.
这就是为什么你必须用它来杀死野兽
Which is why you must use it to slay the beast
这样同样的命运就不会降临到伊丽莎白身上
so that the same fate does not befall upon Elizabeth.
你能说话吗
Can you talk?
你知道马里之洼的人想让我安然无恙  对吧
You know Malivore wants me in one piece, right?
也许我们可以找个更舒服的
So maybe we could find a more comfortable way
方式去传送门那
for me to get to the portal.
咒语
HOPE: Crescere arbor.
霍普
Hope!
- 霍普·迈克尔森  - 这里  来这里
Hope Mikaelson. Here, come here.
- 到身后来  - 到身后来  这就是你现在
Get behind me. "Get behind..." Is that really
- 要说的吗  - 我们现在能不吵吗
all you have to say right now? Can we not do this right now?
如果可以的话  我们甚至
We wouldn't even be having this conversation
都不用进行这样的谈话
if you could have your way.
咒语
Ventus.
听着  我没告诉你是因为我以为你很快乐
Look, I didn't tell you because I thought that you were happy.
- 开心蛋  - 没有你吗
Happier.Without you?
足够开心地做爱
Happy enough to have sex.
那是肯定没有我
That was definitely gonna be without me.
- 谁告诉你的  - 这有关系吗
Who told you that? Does it matter?
你们俩在吵架是好事
Good thing you guys were arguing.
我从城市的另一头都能听到你们的声音
I could hear you from across town.
这是从创造出这个怪物的女巫那拿到的
This belonged to that witch that created that thing,
- 你可能  - 咒语
- so maybe you...   - Finis habentis maleficia.
结局总是这样
You know, something like that.
好了
Okay.
现在我们可以谈谈了
Now we can talk.
你确定你没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事  我很好
Yeah, I'm good.
只是我的
Just my...
头还晕晕的
head is still spinning a little.
好吧  就像我之前说的你真的吓死我了
Well, as I was saying before you scared the hell out of me,
多诺万市长为你担保  你可以走了
Mayor Donovan vouched for you, so you're free to go.
听我的话
Take my advice,
去医院看看
it'd be to a hospital.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我可能用力过猛了
I probably pushed too hard.
但就是有种预感总觉得这个小镇好像有些不对劲
But it's like I know something is off about this town.
也许是其中有一部分觉得是因为你的缘故吧
And maybe part of me wanted to think it's you,
因为
because...
那样我就不用面对
then I wouldn't have to deal with the fact that I'm...
我非常喜欢你这个事实了
extremely attracted to you.
老实说
If I'm being honest...
我也有同感
I feel the same way.
所以我才瞒着你
And that's why I've been keeping things from you.
瞒什么
What things?
酒吧里发生的事情
What happened at the bar,
这不是动物干的
it wasn't the work of an animal.
那是什么
Then what was it?
我猜
My best guess...
是个僵尸
...is that it was a zombie.
也可能是吸血鬼  不是有很多吸血鬼
Or a vampire-- there are plenty of those
在这地方跑来跑去的么
running around here, too, because
况且神秘瀑布镇已经存在了几个世纪了
supernatural beings have existed in Mystic Falls for centuries.
你以为我会信你说的这些吗
Do you expect me to believe that?
恰恰相反
Quite the opposite.
如果要是以我自己的方式
If I allowed myself to care about you
去关心你的话  我会
the way I want to, I would tell you
让你离开这个地方的
to leave this place behind.
但事实是  我需要一个同伴
But the truth is, I need a partner.
一个当我需要她的时候总会看向好的一面的警长
A sheriff who will look the other way when I need her to.
她会永远相信我说的那些
Who will always believe everything I say.
那也不会是我的  里克
That'll never be me, Ric.
我知道
I know.
这是凯勒布
This is Kaleb.
他是吸血鬼
He's a vampire.
他是个青少年
He's a teenager.
你说的对
You're right.
我很抱歉把事情搞得这么复杂
I'm sorry for making this more complicated than that.
不会有下次了
It won't happen again.
教授想让你忘记
Dr. S wants you to forget
关于吸血鬼  女巫  狼人  所有这些超自然生物
everything you know about vampires, witches,
的一切
werewolves-- all supernatural life.
那你现在想起来了吗
So you remember now?
不劳烦你了
No thanks to you.
我会自己解决这些事情
I had to figure out everything on my own.
好吧  你也没告诉我霍普的事情
Well, you didn't tell me about Hope, either.
所以我们扯平了
So we're even.
你是怎么知道的
How did you find out?
我找到了佩内洛普的日记
I found Penelope's journal.
我以为我们早就和那个女巫没关系了
I thought we were done with that witch.
那你最好别再用
Well, then you should
她给你的那支笔了
probably stop using that pen she gave you.
它会记录下你写进日记的每件事
It records everything that you put in your diary.
包括
Including the fact
我从你记忆中净化奥尼这件事
that when I purged the Oni from your mind,
它带回了你所有关于霍普的记忆
it brought back all of your memories of Hope.
现在我的身体已经不受控制
* Now my body and mind are so distant... *
你得解释清楚
You should have said something.
我知道
I know.
我想保护你
I wanted to protect you.
我知道
I know.
而我内心的一部分
And a part of me didn't want
也不想唤回所有人的记忆
to bring back everyone's memories.
我和妈妈谈了谈
But I talked to Mom.
她说人们应该记住自己的过往
And she said that people deserve to know the truth.
呼吸
* Breathe... *
做出他们自己的选择
Make their own choices.
即使会受伤
Even if they hurt.
我无法呼吸
* I can't breathe... *
你觉得兰登会做何选择
What choice do you think Landon's gonna make?
我不能
* I can't... *
我不知道
I don't know.
不管怎样
But I will be here for you
我都会一直陪着你
either way.
喔喔喔喔
* Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh *
喔喔
* Ooh, ooh *
有一个条件
On one condition.
我们之间别再有秘密了
No more secrets.
* Ooh, ooh... *
这话听起来挺在理的
That sounds reasonable.
我的天呐  这算是小插曲吗
Oh, God, I'm having an episode.
至少是个
At least this one's
帅哥来客串
got a hot guy guest star.
等等
Wait.
你可以看见他吗
You can see him?
所有人都可以
Everyone can.
当我的思想不再像我自己
* When my thoughts never feel like my own... *
我有事要告诉你
There's something I need to tell you.
我无法呼吸
* I can't breathe. *
孤身作战是吧
Doing the whole lone wolf thing, huh?
相信我  我懂的
I get it, trust me.
坐吧
Then take a seat.
不行
I can't.
当我变成狼的时候
Um, when I was, uh, stuck as a wolf...
你知道的  兰登为了我做了他可以做的
...you know, Landon did everything he could
一切事情
to bring me back.
我是说  他一直在照顾我
I mean, he's always looked out for me.
我得报答这份恩情
I-I gotta return the favor.
怎么报答
How?
通过
By, um...
我承认我一直喜欢你
owning up to the fact that I've always had feelings for you.
而现在我
And now that I...
我
I...
我记得他们
I remember them.
所以
So...
我们不能再在一起了
...we can't be around each other anymore.
对不起
I'm sorry.
看得出来你在沉思
Looks like you're deep in thought.
更像是在为即将告诉你的事儿给自己打气
More like steeling myself for what I have to tell you.
我从未有过一刻把你忘记
* There's never been a moment you were forgotten *
你并非不可救药
* You are not hopeless... *
看来你不是去里士满实地考察了
So I take it you weren't on a field trip to Richmond?
也没了纯真
* Your innocence stolen... *
我去新奥尔良了
Um, I was in New Orleans.
我需要去找个女巫
I needed to find a witch.
这儿也有很多女巫阿
There's plenty of those around here.
迈克尔森家族的女巫
Mikaelson witch.
霍普的姑妈
Hope's aunt.
我需要答案
I needed answers.
我需要一个推力才能继续做正确的事
I needed a push to do the right thing.
带回每个人的记忆
Bring back everyone's memories.
我会派一支军队
* I will send out an army... *
霍普的家族也失去了他们生活中的某些记忆
Hope's family was missing a piece of their life, too.
黑夜里  真的
* Night, it's true... *
我得亲眼看看
I needed to see that for myself,
这样我就不会那么自私了
so I would stop being so selfish.
你是我见过的
You are literally the least selfish person
最不自私的人了
I've ever met.
我无需记这些
That's nothing I had to remember.
一次又一次
* Over and over... *
因为这是我永远不会忘记的事情
'Cause it's something I'll never forget.
我就是你的避风港
* I'll be your shelter *
我就是你的盔甲
* I'll be your armor... *
但你记得她
But you do remember her.
这改变了一切  对吧
That changes things, right?
我不知道
I don't know yet.
我听到了你的求助声
* I hear your S.O.S... *
我需要些时间
I just need some time.
你的求助声
* Your S.O.S... *
我只是
I just...
需要些时间
need time.
去把你寻找
* To find you in the middle *
在沉寂的黑夜里
* Of the darkest night, it's true... *
好
Yeah, of course.
我会把你拯救
* I will rescue you *
我会派一支军队
* I will send out an army *
去把你寻找
* To find you in the middle *
在沉寂的黑夜里
* Of the darkest night... *
霍普
Hope?
我会拯救你
* I will rescue you *
弗雷娅姑姑
Aunt Freya?
我永远不会
* I will never stop *
停止寻觅你
* Marching to reach you *
尽管身处艰难的挣扎中
* In the middle of the hardest *
真的
* Fight, it's true *
我会把你拯救
* I will rescue you *
* Oh, I will rescue you. *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）